Girls' Night Out is a thriller, tv movie film directed by Philippe Gagnon.
McKenzie is a few months away from getting married when her three best
friends from college surprise her with a bachelorette party.
Sadie, played by Katherine Barrell.
MacKenzie, played by Mackenzie Mauzy.
Joelle, played by Kelly Kruger.
Rebecca, played by Hannah Emily Anderson.
Reese, played by Cody Ray Thompson.
Brandon, played by Jacob Blair.
Rough Night is a 2017 American black comedy film directed by Lucia Aniello
(in her feature debut) and written by Aniello and Paul W.
It stars Scarlett Johansson, Kate McKinnon, Jillian Bell, Ilana Glazer and Zoë Kravitz in lead
roles, as well as Paul Downs, Ty Burrell and Demi Moore in supporting roles.
The story follows a bachelorette party that goes
wrong after a male stripper dies.
The film was released in the United States on June 16, 2017, by Sony Pictures Releasing through Columbia Pictures,
received mixed reviews and grossed $47 million worldwide against a production budget of about $26 million.
The tone is intense.